{
    "questions": [
      {
        "id":1,
        "question": "1Who is the highest run-scorer in Test cricket?",
        "options": [
          "Sachin Tendulkar",
          "Ricky Ponting",
          "Virat Kohli",
          "Alastair Cook"
        ],
        "answer": "Sachin Tendulkar"
      },
      {
        "id":2,
        "question": "2Which bowler has taken the most wickets in Test cricket?",
        "options": [
          "Muttiah Muralitharan",
          "Shane Warne",
          "Anil Kumble",
          "James Anderson"
        ],
        "answer": "Muttiah Muralitharan"
      },
      {
        "id":3,
        "question": "3Who is the fastest player to score 10,000 runs in One Day Internationals (ODIs)?",
        "options": [
          "Sachin Tendulkar",
          "Virat Kohli",
          "Ricky Ponting",
          "Brian Lara"
        ],
        "answer": "Virat Kohli"
      },
      {
        "id":4,
        "question": "4Which country has won the most Cricket World Cup titles?",
        "options": [
          "Australia",
          "India",
          "West Indies",
          "England"
        ],
        "answer": "Australia"
      },
      {
        "id":5,
        "question": "5Who is the only player to score 400 runs in a single Test innings?",
        "options": [
          "Brian Lara",
          "Matthew Hayden",
          "Kumar Sangakkara",
          "Virender Sehwag"
        ],
        "answer": "Brian Lara"
      },
      {
        "id":6,
        "question": "6Who has scored the most centuries in international cricket?",
        "options": [
          "Sachin Tendulkar",
          "Virat Kohli",
          "Ricky Ponting",
          "Kumar Sangakkara"
        ],
        "answer": "Sachin Tendulkar"
      },
      {
        "id":7,
        "question": "7Which team has won the most ICC Champions Trophy titles?",
        "options": [
          "Australia",
          "India",
          "West Indies",
          "South Africa"
        ],
        "answer": "India"
      },
      {
        "id":8,
        "question": "8Who is the fastest bowler to reach 100 wickets in One Day Internationals (ODIs)?",
        "options": [
          "Mitchell Starc",
          "Saqlain Mushtaq",
          "Dennis Lillee",
          "Rashid Khan"
        ],
        "answer": "Saqlain Mushtaq"
      },
      {
        "id":9,
        "question": "9Which player has hit the most sixes in the history of T20 internationals?",
        "options": [
          "Chris Gayle",
          "Rohit Sharma",
          "Brendon McCullum",
          "Martin Guptill"
        ],
        "answer": "Chris Gayle"
      },
      {
        "id":10,
        "question": "10Who is the only cricketer to score a century and take 10 wickets in the same Test match?",
        "options": [
          "Imran Khan",
          "Kapil Dev",
          "Shane Watson",
          "Ben Stokes"
        ],
        "answer": "Imran Khan"
      },
      {
        "id":11,
        "question": "11Who is the highest wicket-taker in T20 international cricket?",
        "options": [
          "Lasith Malinga",
          "Shahid Afridi",
          "Saeed Ajmal",
          "Umar Gul"
        ],
        "answer": "Lasith Malinga"
      }
    ]
  
}